const words = [
  { front: "각골", back: ["난망", "통한"] },
  { front: "각자", back: "도생" },
  { front: "감개", back: "무량" },
  { front: "감언", back: ["이설", "지지"] },
  { front: "감지", back: ["덕지", "센서", "능력"] },
  { front: "갑론", back: "을박" },
  { front: "강강", back: "술래" },
  { front: "개과", back: ["천선", "불린"] },
  { front: "과테", back: "말라" },
  { front: "거두", back: "절미" },
  { front: "경거", back: "망동" },
  { front: "경국", back: ["지색", "제세", "지재"] },
  { front: "결초", back: "보은" },
  { front: "게르", back: ["마늄", "만족"] },
  { front: "고군", back: "분투" },
  { front: "고슴", back: "도치" },
  { front: "고진", back: "감래" },
  { front: "과유", back: "불급" },
  { front: "군계", back: "일학" },
  { front: "권모", back: "술수" },
  { front: "권선", back: "징악" },
  { front: "구사", back: "일생" },
  { front: "근묵", back: "자흑" },
  { front: "금시", back: ["초문", "발복"] },
  { front: "금의", back: ["환향", "야행", "옥식"] },
  { front: "기고", back: "만장" },
  { front: "기진", back: "맥진" },
  { front: "나폴", back: ["레옹", "리탄"] },
  { front: "남산", back: "타워" },
  { front: "난공", back: "불락" },
  { front: "네덜", back: "란드" },
  { front: "노르", back: "웨이" },
  { front: "노심", back: "초사" },
  { front: "누네", back: "띠네" },
  { front: "뉴발", back: "란스" },
  { front: "뉴질", back: "랜드" },
  { front: "다사", back: "다난" },
  { front: "대한", back: ["민국", "항공"] },
  { front: "도원", back: "결의" },
  { front: "독불", back: "장군" },
  { front: "동문", back: ["서답", "회장", "시장"] },
  { front: "동병", back: "상련" },
  { front: "또오", back: "해영" },
  { front: "뚜레", back: "쥬르" },
  { front: "라즈", back: "베리" },
  { front: "랩몬", back: "스터" },
  { front: "런천", back: "미트" },
  { front: "막상", back: "막하" },
  { front: "만리", back: "장성" },
  { front: "만신", back: "창이" },
  { front: "망연", back: "자실" },
  { front: "맥도", back: "날드" },
  { front: "맥수", back: "지탄" },
  { front: "명불", back: "허전" },
  { front: "명실", back: "상부" },
  { front: "무념", back: "무상" },
  { front: "무릉", back: "도원" },
  { front: "무아", back: ["지경", "도취"] },
  { front: "무용", back: ["지물", "지용"] },
  { front: "문전", back: ["성시", "걸식", "옥답"] },
  { front: "박테", back: ["리아", "로신"] },
  { front: "방방", back: "곡곡" },
  { front: "배은", back: "망덕" },
  { front: "백년", back: ["가약", "대계", "해로", "하청"] },
  { front: "버벌", back: "진트" },
  { front: "벽력", back: "일섬" },
  { front: "보노", back: "보노" },
  { front: "복세", back: "편살" },
  { front: "볼리", back: ["비아", "베어"] },
  { front: "불가", back: ["리아", "리스", "사리", "사의"] },
  { front: "붉은", back: ["노을", "악마"] },
  { front: "비선", back: ["실세", "형적", "형성", "광도"] },
  { front: "비트", back: ["코인", "연산", "박스"] },
  { front: "빌게", back: "이츠" },
  { front: "샌드", back: ["위치", "박스"] },
  { front: "생년", back: "월일" },
  { front: "선글", back: "라스" },
  { front: "성균", back: "관대" },
  { front: "셜록", back: "홈즈" },
  { front: "셀트", back: "리온" },
  { front: "술래", back: "잡기" },
  { front: "스리", back: ["랑카", "라차", "반정"] },
  {
    front: "스타",
    back: [
      "워즈",
      "필드",
      "벅스",
      "일러",
      "일링",
      "시티",
      "리아",
      "렉스",
      "디움",
    ],
  },
  { front: "스파", back: ["게티", "이더", "르타", "이스", "이시", "이크"] },
  { front: "스핑", back: ["크스", "고신"] },
  { front: "쓰레", back: ["기통", "기장"] },
  { front: "싱가", back: "포르" },
  { front: "아나", back: ["운서", "콘다"] },
  { front: "알고", back: "리즘" },
  { front: "알레", back: ["르기", "르망", "그로"] },
  { front: "알래", back: ["스카", "스터"] },
  { front: "알리", back: ["스타", "바바", "바이"] },
  { front: "어린", back: ["이날", "이집", "왕자"] },
  { front: "어장", back: "관리" },
  { front: "얼그", back: "레이" },
  { front: "업데", back: "이트" },
  { front: "에콰", back: "도르" },
  { front: "온두", back: "라스" },
  { front: "우루", back: "과이" },
  { front: "웰시", back: "코기" },
  { front: "이탈", back: "리아" },
  { front: "자메", back: "이카" },
  { front: "장칼", back: "국수" },
  { front: "제네", back: "시스" },
  { front: "조팝", back: "나무" },
  { front: "즐겨", back: "찾기" },
  { front: "짐바", back: "브웨" },
  { front: "짜파", back: ["게티", "구리"] },
  { front: "카놀", back: "라유" },
  { front: "카멜", back: ["레온", "리아"] },
  { front: "카스", back: ["테라", "타드", "토퍼"] },
  { front: "캄보", back: "디아" },
  { front: "캡사", back: "이신" },
  { front: "코스", back: ["모스", "요리", "이탈", "프레"] },
  { front: "콜로", back: ["세움", "라도"] },
  { front: "콜롬", back: ["비아", "버스"] },
  { front: "퀴리", back: "부인" },
  { front: "퀵서", back: "비스" },
  { front: "토네", back: "이도" },
  { front: "토마", back: ["호크", "토마"] },
  { front: "톨게", back: "이트" },
  { front: "톱니", back: "바퀴" },
  { front: "튀르", back: "키예" },
  { front: "파키", back: "스탄" },
  { front: "풀하", back: "우스" },
  { front: "폼클", back: ["렌징", "렌저", "렌져"] },
  { front: "피노", back: "키오" },
  { front: "함무", back: "라비" },
  { front: "해바", back: "라기" },
  { front: "호랑", back: ["나비", "이굴"] },
  { front: "헬리", back: ["콥터", "코일", "오스", "녹스"] },
  { front: "헬렌", back: "켈러" },
  { front: "홈페", back: "이지" },
];
export default words;
